{
    "id": "688c4d48b38a4859a431d7ff60da91ec",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "........................................... many members have expressed concerns regarding the viability of the project, what will happen to it?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Now",
                "That",
                "Now that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My child falls ill ......................................... there is a slight change in the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when",
                "whenever"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t have to wait ............................................ you are in a hurry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will buy the car ................................................. they reduce their asking price.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. there is an emergency, ring",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In case",
                "In case of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The bank will make the loan .............................................. we pledge our jewels.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "supposing that",
                "provided that",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................ I am not able to sleep, I take the tablet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care what job you do ................................................ you are happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "no  sooner than",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................. she read the telegram, she started crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Provided that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can go out to play .................................................... you finish your homework first.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "provided that",
                "as soon as",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}